Oh,look! There's Joey's picture!
你们看，是乔伊的照片
This is so exciting!
真是令人兴奋
You can spot someone who's never seen his plays.
你总是能看见 从未在自己作品中出现的某人
Notice,no fear. No sense of impending doom.
注意力强，无畏无惧
"The role of man number three will not be played by Vic Shapiro. "
"三号男演员不能让维克.夏皮罗演"
We came on the wrong night.
看来我们来错时间了啊.
I can't believe I forgot a magazine.
不敢相信我居然把杂志忘了
-Come on,this might be good. -I don't know.
-这样也许更好一些 -我不知道
The exclamation point scares me. It's not just Freud,it's Freud!
标题上的惊叹号让我害怕 这不只是佛洛依德,而是佛洛依德!
Magic is about to happen!
奇迹就要出现
Well,Eva...
伊娃
...we've done some excellent work here.
你今天的表现不错
And I would have to say...
我得说……
...your problem is quite clear.
……你的问题相当清楚
All you want is a dinkle
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
To play with or simply let hang
The One With the Butt
六人行 第1季 第06集 屁股秀
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
I feel violated.
我感觉自己受到冒犯了
Did anybody else feel like peeling their skin off...
还有其他人感觉只想剥自己的皮
...to have something else to do?
如果他们还有其他事可做?
Ross,1 0:00.
罗斯，十点钟
Is it? It feels like 2.
是吗?感觉像是两点
-No,1 0:00! -What?
-不，十点钟 -什么?
There's a beautiful woman at 8,9,1 0:00!
一位美女在8，9，10点钟方向
Hello!
你!
She's amazing! She makes the women l dream about look like fat,bald men.
她简直就是仙女下凡 她让我的梦中情人变得有如矮胖的秃子
Go over. She's not with anyone.
过去啊，她旁边没人
And what would my opening line be? Excuse me....
对，我该用什么开场白? 对不起,啦啦啦啦之类的
Come on,she's a person. You can do it.
拜托，她只是个人，你罩得住
Could she be more out of my league? Back me up.
请告诉我，我配得上她吗? 罗斯，帮我壮壮胆
He couldn't get a woman like that in a million years.
他这副德行一辈子都别想把到这种美女
You always see these beautiful women with "nothing" guys.
但这种美女,身边总是跟着蹩脚货
You could be one of those guys.
你也可以成为其中之一
-You could do that. -You think?
-没错，你能办到 -你也认为?
Absolutely!
是的.
I can't believe I'm considering this.
没想到我竟有这种念头
-l' m very aware of my tongue. -Come on.
-我一向谨言慎行 -快去
Here goes.
我上了
Stand back,everyone. Incoming ego shrapnel.
退后，伙计.炮火来袭.
All right,I can do this.
好的，我能做到的
-Yes? -Hi.
-怎么? -嗨.
Okay,next word would be...
下个字是…
... Chandler.
…钱德
Chandler is my name and....
我叫钱德
Hi!
Yes,you said that.
我知道，你说过
Yes! Yes,I did. But what I didn't say....
对，我说过 但我没说我想说...
What I wanted to say was...
我想说的是……
...would you like to go out with me? Thank you. Good night.
……愿意与我约会吗? 谢谢，晚安
Chandler?
钱德
-I didn't know you could dance! -You were in a play!
-想不到你会跳舞 -你演戏了
What'd you think?
感觉如何?
-I didn't know you could dance! -You were in a play!
-想不到你会跳舞 -你演戏了
It wasn't that bad. I was the lead.
拜托，没那么糟吧 我是主角
It was better than the troll thing. At least you got to see my head.
这次我在轮唱中出现 至少你们可以看见我的头
-You're right. -We saw your head.
-对没错 -我们有看见你的头
How about that accent?
这德国口音怎么样?
Yeah. All of your W's were V's.
不错，你的W全变成V了
She said yes!
她答应了…
Awful play,man!
好烂的戏
Her name's Aurora. She's ltalian and she pronounces my name " Chandler. "
她叫亚萝拉，来自意大利 她叫我”Chandlerrrrrrr”
I like that better.
我喜欢她这样称呼我
The usher gave me this.
领座员要我把它交给你
-What is it? -The Estelle Leonard T alent Agency.
-这是什么? -Estelle Leonard经纪公司
An agency left its card. They wanna sign me!
经纪公司拿名片给我 或许他们想和我签约
Based on this play?
因为这场戏?
Based on this play!
因为这一场戏
Look! There's a note on the back.
瞧!背面有字
"Loved your work. Call me a sap. "
"喜欢你的工作.请叫我挖墙脚的"
She was obviously very moved!
显然她非常的动人
You should call her fairly quickly.
你应该马上打电话给她
Yeah! As soon as possible!
越快越好
Come in!
请进
Hi. I'm here to see Estelle Leonard.
Hi.我来找Estelle.Leonard的.
Just a moment,let me see if she's in.
等等，让我看看如果她进来……
Hello.
你好.
-You' re Estelle? -I know...
-你是Estelle? -我知道……
...you weren't expecting someone so fantastically beautiful.
……你在等 一位如此美丽动人的小姐.
Love lump. T ake a load off already, darling. Sit already.
笨小伙.放下负担 亲爱的,坐下来
I can't tell you how excited I am to be here.
我无法用语言表述 到这里来我有多么兴奋
Why not?
为什么?
-What I meant was -You don't mind if I eat,do you?
-我的意思是说 -你不介意我边吃边听吧
Joey...
...sweetheart,let me ask you a question.
……让我问你一个问题
Did you ever see the movie Sleepless in Seattle?
你看过"西雅图未眠夜"这部电影吗?
-Wow! Do you represent those actors? -No.
-没. -喔!你要我扮演那些演员 -不是这样的.
But you know the end, where they' re happy?
你知道结尾的，最后他们快乐的在一起
That's gonna be you and me.
那将是你和我
You mean you wanna sign me?
你是说你准备和我签约
No,I wanna go to the top of the Empire State Building and make out.
不，我要到帝国大厦顶搂去说明.
Of course I wanna sign you!
我当然是要签你啊!
-Miss Leonard,I'm so -Oh,boy.
小姐,我实在是 -Oh,小伙子
-Ride them,cowboy. -l' m sorry!
-坐在那里,牛仔.  -对不起!
I don't see it!
我看不到
-T ry to look through it. -Unfocus your eyes.
-试着看这里  -让你的眼睛离焦.
Focus? There's nothing to focus on.
集中?没有什么东西可以集中眼力
-It's the Statue of Liberty! -Right!
-是自由女神 -对啦
-Where's the Statue of Liberty? -There.
-自由女神在哪里? -那里.
I can't not see it now.
现在我看不到了
Hey,kids!
嗨，小子!
Come here. Do you see anything here?
到这里来.你在这里看到什么了吗?
-lt looks like a boat. -A boat.
-看起来像一只船 -一只船.
Right in front of the Statue of Liberty.
正好在自由女神前面
It's been seven seconds,and you haven't asked me how my date went.
我坐在这儿都七秒钟了 竟没人问我的约会如何?
How was your date,Chandler?
你的约会如何，钱德?
It was unbelievable!
真是令人难以置信
I've never met anyone like her. She's had an amazing life!
我没见过像她那样的人 她的生活真是太令人称羡了
She was in the Israeli army.
她穿过以色列阵地
None of the bullets hit the engine, so we made it to the border.
幸好子弹没打中引擎 我们才能越过边界
But just barely,and l....
真是有惊无险
I've been talking about myself all night long. I'm sorry.
我整晚都在谈我自己，抱歉
What about you? T ell me a story.
你呢?说来听听嘛
All right,once...
有一回...
... I got on the subway.
我搭地铁
And it was at night...
是在晚上
...and I rode it all the way to Brooklyn.
...那晚我搭地铁到布鲁克林区
Just for the hell of it.
然后活著回来
We talked until 2:00. It was perfect.
我们一直谈到两点,那真是个美好的夜晚
More or less.
可以这么说
Suddenly,we realized we were in Yemen.
突然我们发现自己身在也门
I' m sorry,so "we" is...?
我们,我们是谁?
"We" is me and Rick.
我和瑞克
Who's Rick?
瑞克是谁?
My husband.
我丈夫
-Oh,so you' re divorced? -No.
-这么说你们已经离婚 -没有
I' m sorry. So you' re widowed? Hopefully?
对不起，这么说你是寡妇? 希望如此
No,l' m still married.
不，我们还是夫妻
So,how would your husband feel about you sitting here with me...
告诉我你丈夫做何感想? 你坐在我身旁...
...sliding your foot so far up my leg you can count the change in my pocket?
...脚伸到我大腿 足以数我口袋里的零钱?
Don't worry.
别担心，
He'd be okay with you because he's okay with Ethan.
我想他会接受的 因为他也接受伊森这么做
Ethan? There's an Ethan?
伊森?有伊森这号人物?
Ethan is my boyfriend.
伊森是我的男友
What?
什么?
What kind of relationship do you imagine us having...
告诉我你期待我们之间会有什么关系...
...if you have a husband and a boyfriend?
既然你已有丈夫和男友
I suppose,mainly sexual.
大概是性关系吧
Sorry it didn't work out.
真是遗憾，你们吹了
What,not work out? I'm seeing her again on Thursday.
什么,吹了? 周四我还要和她约会
Didn't you listen to the story?
难道你没听懂?
Didn't you listen? It's twisted!
难道你没听懂?这太离谱了
How could you get involved with her?
你怎能和这种女人交往?
I had trouble with it at first. But I get the good stuff.
开始我也无法接受 但后来我想此事百益而无一害
All the fun,all the talking, all the sex...
只有谈天说笑和做爱...
...and none of the responsibility.
不用负任何责任
-This is every guy's fantasy! -That's not true!
-这是每个男人的梦想 -是吗?未必吧
-Ross,is this your fantasy? -No,of course not.
-罗斯，这是你的梦想吗? -当然不是
Yeah. Yeah,it is.
没错，是
You'd go out with someone going out with someone else?
你们男生不介意 和已有对象的女人交往?
-I couldn't. -Good for you.
-我办不到 -干得好，乔伊
When l' m with a woman, I need to know...
和女人交往时,我必须确定...
... I' m going out with more people than her.
...我交往的对象比她多
Once,I went out with a guy who just got divorced.
一次我和一个刚离婚的家伙出去
It was hard. His kids liked me better than him.
这很麻烦.相比之下 他的孩子更喜欢我一些
What does this have to do with Chandler?
钱德必须作些什么呢?
Nothing.
什么也不用.
I didn't have anything on that topic.
关于这个话题我什么都不想说
So I went another way.
好吧，我换一种方法
You know,monogamy can be a tricky concept.
你知道,一夫一妻值得商榷
I mean,anthropologically speaking
就人类学的观点而言…
Fine. Now you'll never know.
行…这是你们的损失
We' re kidding. T ell us.
逗你的，告诉我们吧
-We wanna know. -Come on!
-我们想知道 -快说，
All right. There's a theory put forth by Richard Leakey
好吧理查李奇提出这样的理论…
Are we greeting each other this way now? I like it.
现在都这样打招呼吗?我喜欢
Look! I cleaned!
瞧，我大扫除了
I did the windows. I did the floors.
我擦窗户，拖地板
I used all the vacuum attachments but the round one. What's it for?
我甚至还用了吸尘器上的所有装置 圆形有鬃毛那个除外,我不知道怎么用?
Nobody knows. And we're not supposed to ask.
没人知道，我们也不该问
What do you think?
你们感觉怎样?
-It's very clean. -Really,it looks great!
-很干净 -真的看起来不错
I see you moved the green ottoman.
你移动了绿色的垫椅
How did that happen?
怎么会呢?
I don't know. It looked better there.
我不知道,我以为摆那儿会更好看
And it's an extra seat around the table.
咖啡桌旁就多了一个座位
Yeah,it's interesting.
这倒有意思
But you know what? Just for fun...
这样好了，只是好玩...
...Iet's see what it looked like in the old spot.
...我们看它在原来位置的感觉如何
Just to compare.
只是做个比较
Let's see.
让我看看
Well,it looks good there too.
放那儿也不错
Let's leave it there for a while.
就摆那儿一阵子吧
I can't believe you moved the green ottoman.
我无法相信你竟敢搬动了绿色垫椅
Be glad you didn't fan the magazines. She'll scratch your eyes out.
幸好你没摊开杂志 否则她铁定会挖出你的眼睛
-You guys,I am not that bad! -Yeah,you are.
-各位，我没那么凶吧 -你就那么凶
Remember,I lived with you? You were a little....
记得我们住在一起时吗? 你就像个…
That is so unfair!
这太不公平了
When we were kids,yours was the only Raggedy Ann doll that wasn't raggedy.
拜托，我们小时候 你的“破娃娃”是唯一不破的
Okay,so I'm responsible. I'm organized.
我有责任感有组织性
But hey,I can be a kook!
可是我也能很懒散
All right,you madcap gal!
好吧，懒女人，
Imagine this.
想像这个情况
The phone bill arrives, but you don't pay it right away.
电话单来 但你不立刻去交钱
-Why not? -Because you're a kook!
-为什么? -因为你是个大懒人
You wait until they send a notice.
直拖到他们寄催缴通知单来
I could do that.
我可以办到
Okay,then you let me go grocery shopping
你让我去买日常用品
-No problem. -I'm not done yet.
-没问题 -我还没说完
And I buy detergent,but it's not the one with the easy-pour spout.
我买了洗衣粉, 但是是不容易弄出来那种.
Why would someone do that?
有人会那样做吗?
One might wonder.
有人会想…
But I would be fine with that.
我就没有问题
A glass is on the table with no coaster. A cold drink. A hot day.
有人在咖啡桌上留下杯子 没有垫子,天气很热,一杯冷饮
Beads of condensation are inching closer to the wood....
小水珠逐渐逼近桌面…
Stop it!
够了
Oh,my God!
天啊，
It's true. Who am l?
没错，我到是谁?
Monica,you' re Mom.
摩妮卡，你是妈妈那样的.
Oh,my God!
天啊，
Okay,I'll be there.
好，我会去的
That was my agent.
我的经纪人打来的
My agent has just gotten me a job in the new Al Pacino movie!
他安排我在艾尔帕西诺的新片中演出
-That's great! -What's the part?
-太棒了… -演什么角色?
Can you believe it? Pacino! This guy's why I became an actor!
你们能相信吗?是艾尔帕西诺 我就是喜欢他才立志要当演员
" Out of order? You' re out of order! This whole courtroom's out of order! "
"我失控，你也失控" 这整个法庭都失控了
Seriously,what's the part?
言归正传，什么角色?
"Just when I thought I was out, they pull me back in! "
当我认为已出局时 他们却又将我拉回
Come on. Seriously,Joey, what's the part?
快老实说，什么角色?
You' re.... What?
你是…什么?
I' m his butt double,okay?
我是他臀部的替身
I play Al Pacino's butt.
我演艾尔帕西诺的臀部
All right? He goes into the shower, and then...
他走进浴室,然后...
... I' m his butt.
...我就是他的屁股
Oh,my God!
天那
Come on,you guys.
别这样
It's a real Pacino movie and that's big!
这是一部艾尔帕西诺主演大制作的电影
It's terrific. You deserve this.
别误会，这真是太棒了 这是你应得的
After years of struggling you've cracked your way into show business.
这是你多年努力的成果 你终于能登上大银幕
Fine. Make jokes,I don't care.
行，笑吧，我不在乎
-This is a big break for me! -You' re right. It is.
-这是我千载难逢的机会 -没错，
So,will you invite us to the big opening?
你准备邀请我们参加你的首映会吗?
-I need some moisturizer. -For what?
-我得向你借些保湿乳液 -干什么呢?
T oday's the big day!
今天可是我的大日子
You got any tweezers? I think I have a rogue hair.
你有镊子吗?我得毛发太乱啦
God. Go in the bathroom. Use whatever you want.
好吧，进浴室要用什么自己拿
Don't ever tell me what you did in there.
只是别告诉我你在里面干什么
Thank you.
谢谢
-Joey's mom's on the phone. -ln the bathroom.
-乔伊在哪儿?他妈打电话来 -他在浴室里，
-You don't wanna go in there! -Come on,we' re roommates.
-你最好别进去 -拜托，我们是室友
My eyes! My eyes!
我的眼睛!我的眼睛!
I warned you.
我警告过你
Who is being loud?
谁在大吼大叫
Oh,that would be Monica.
一定是摩妮卡
Can I borrow stuff? I wanna make Aurora breakfast.
我能借点东西吗? 我想为她做早点
You got the whole night?
她陪你一夜?
Well,I only have 20 minutes until Ethan,so....
没错，我们只剩20分钟 直到伊森…
Do I sense resentment?
难道我感到怨恨?
No. No resentment. Believe me...
不，没有怨恨，相信我……
...it's worth it,okay?
……绝对值得
In a relationship,you have moments you'll remember the rest of your life.
在你交往的过程中 有多少重要的时刻 会让你怀念一辈子?
Every single second is like that with Aurora.
与萝拉相处的每一秒都是
I've just wasted 35 of them talking to you.
而我已浪费35秒和你们说话
So,Monica,can you help me with the door?
摩妮卡请帮我开门
The old Monica would remind you...
钱德，老摩妮卡会提醒你
...to scrub that T eflon pan with a plastic brush.
……用塑胶刷刷特弗龙锅
But l' m not gonna do that.
但我不会那么做的
Excuse me? Can they warm it up? I' m concerned about goose bumps.
不好意思?他们热身的怎么样了? 我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
Everybody ready?
大家准备好没?
I wanna thank you for this opportunity.
我只是想感谢你给我这个机会
I mean,I know this is just a first step,but I hope that someday
我是说,我知道这只是第一步 但是我期待有一天
Lose the robe.
解开浴袍
Right. Okay. Losing the robe!
好，我正解开浴袍
Okay,and the robe is lost.
浴袍已解开
I would like to get this in one take.
各位，我想一次解决
Let's roll it.
来吧，
Water's working.
放水
And action!
开始!
And cut!
停!
Butt guy,what are you doing?
屁股男，你在干什么?
I'm showering.
我在洗澡
No,that was clenching.
不，你在挤屁股
The way I see it, the guy's upset here,you know?
我认为他很沮丧
His wife's dead, his brother's missing.
他的太太死了，弟弟失踪了
I think his butt would be angry here.
我想他的屁股一定很愤怒
I think his butt would like to get the shot before lunch.
我想他的屁股会想在午餐前杀青
Once again,rolling. Water working.
再来一次,开机 放水
And action!
开始
And cut! What was that?
停！你又在干什么?
I was going for quiet desperation.
我要表现出绝望
But if you have to ask....
但如果你想问
God,I love these fingers.
天啊，我爱这些手指
Thank you.
谢谢
No,actually,I meant my fingers.
不，我是指我的手指
Look at them. Look at how happy they are.
你瞧它们多开心
-Oh,my God,l' m late! -Oh,no!
-天啊，我来不及了 -天啊, 不
-Don't go. -Okay.
-不要走 -好不好
-I have to. -Look,she's leaving.
-我得走了 -看,她走了
I' m sorry. He'll be waiting for me.
抱歉，他在等我了
-I thought you talked to Rick. -It's not Rick.
-我以为你瑞克谈过 -不是瑞克
Ethan? He gets the whole day!
是伊森?他要陪你一整天
No,it's Andrew.
不是他，是安德鲁
I know there'll be moments...
我知道……
...when I'll regret asking the following question,but....
……我会后悔问你这个问题，但是……
-And Andrew is? -He's...
-这个安德鲁 -他是……
... new.
……新欢
So you' re not completely fulfilled by Rick,Ethan and myself?
你是说瑞克，伊森和我 三人还不能满足你?
No,that's not exactly what I was
我以前不是这种人
Most women would kill...
不知道多少女人……
...for three guys like us.
……被我们三人迷倒
-So,what do you want? -You.
-你想要什么? -你
-You have me. -No. Just you.
-你已拥有我 -不，只是你
-What do you mean? -Lose the other guys.
-什么意思? -甩掉其他人
Like,all of them?
他们全部?
Come on,we' re great together. Why not?
我们这样不是很快乐吗?为什么不行?
Can't we have what we have now?
我们为何不能及时行乐?
Why can't we talk and make love...
为何不能只是聊天,做爱……
...without feeling obligated to each other?
……彼此没有任何负担?
Up until tonight,I thought that's what you wanted too.
今晚之前,我以为这也是你想要的
Well,part of me wants that...
部分的我想要
... but it's like l' m two guys. One guy's saying,"This is great! "
...但我就像是双面人 一个说”闭嘴,这样很好”
But there's this other guy.
但是还有另一个
The guy who wells up when the Grinch's heart grows...
他每回都挺身而出……
...and breaks that measuring device.
……仗义直言
He's saying,you know, "This is too hard. Get out! "
他说“这太丑陋了，快脱身”
So,which one of the guys will you listen to?
你听哪一个的话?
I have to listen to both. They don't let each other finish.
两人的话我得都听 他们争执不休
Which one?
哪一个？
The second guy.
第二个
I see.
好吧，
Call me if you change your mind.
改变主意后再打电话给我吧
Sorry,the first guy runs the lips.
抱歉，第一个动的口
Look at it this way. You dumped her!
这样想吧，你把她甩了
Right? I mean,this woman was unbelievably sexy...
真的?我是说,这女人性感……
...and beautiful,intelligent, unattainable.
……美丽聪明而且遥不可及
T ell me why you did this again?
再告诉我一次,你为何这么做
Movie star!
电影明星他回来了
Wait! Aren't you the guy who plays the butt in the new Pacino movie?
等等，你不是在艾尔帕西诺新片中 演屁股的那个?
Nope.
不是
No? What happened,big guy?
不是?怎么了，大个儿?
Big guy?
大个儿?
It felt like a "big guy" moment.
感觉就像“大个儿”时刻
I got fired!
我被开除了
They said I acted too much with it.
没错，他们说我太投入了
I told everybody about this!
我到处宣扬
-Everybody's expecting to see me. -lKnow what?
-现在大家都想到戏院看我演… -我知道?
-No one will be able to tell. -My mom will.
-乔伊，没人会认出来的 -我妈就认得出来
There's something so sweet and disturbing about that.
真是令人感动又恶心
I've done crappy plays for six years...
六年来我除了演些烂角色一事无成
...and I finally get my shot, and I blow it!
如今机会来了我竟将它搞砸
Maybe this wasn't it.
等等，或许这不是你的机会
I think when it's your shot, you know it's your shot.
机会是否来临自己最清楚
Did it feel like your shot?
你感觉这是你的机会吗?
Hard to tell. I was naked.
很难分辨，我当时全身赤裸
I don't think this was it. I don't think you just get one.
我不认为这是你唯一的机会 你的机会不会只有一个
I believe things are gonna happen for you. I do.
我相信大好机会就降临到你身上
You've got to think about the day some kid will go:
你必须想著 将来有个小伙子跑到朋友面前说
"l got the part! I'm gonna be Joey T ribbiani's ass! "
我被录取了… 我要演乔伊的屁股
You think? That's so nice.
你真好
I' m sorry,Joey. I' m gonna go to bed,guys.
真遗憾，乔伊 各位，我要去睡了
-Good night. -Good night.
-晚安 -晚安
You' re gonna leave your shoes out here?
你要把鞋子留在这儿?
Really? Just casually strewn about...
真的?就这样乱丢?
...in that reckless,haphazard manner?
...就这样轻率的,随意的乱扔?
It doesn't matter. I'll get them tomorrow. Or not!
无所谓 我明天再拿,或者算了
Whenever.
随便
She is a kook.
她真懒散
If it bothers you that much, just go out and get the shoes.
既然这么困扰，就快去拿吧
No,don 't do this!
不，千万别去，
This is stupid!
太愚蠢了
I don 't have to prove anything. I'm gonna get them.
我无须证明什么，我要去拿
But then everyone will know.
但如此一来他们都会知道
Unless I get them,then wake up really early and put them back.
除非我去拿然后早起放回去
I need help!
谁来帮我一把!
-All you want is a dinkle -Not that song!
不要唱这首歌
-All you envy's a schwang -Come on,you guys.
伙计们,不要这样
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang
All you want is a dinkle
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang